In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to make the H consonant sound.
我们将学习如何发出 H 辅音音。
This sound is simply made, H,
这个音很简单，就是 H，
by passing air through a very slightly constricted passage,
通过一个非常轻微收缩的通道让空气通过，
either between the tongue and the roof of the mouth,
要么是在舌头和上颚之间，
H,
H，
or in the throat,
要么是在喉咙里，
H.
H。
This is an unvoiced consonant.
这是一个无声的辅音。
Part the lips and press the tongue down in the back just a little.
分开嘴唇，稍微向下压舌头的后部。
If you don't constrict the air passage at all, there's no sound.
如果你完全不收缩气流通道，就没有声音。
If you lift the back of your tongue and constrict too much,
如果你抬起舌头的后部并收缩得太多，
you'll feel the vibration of the soft palate bouncing on the tongue.
你会感觉到软腭在舌头上振动。
This is too heavy.
这太重了。
The lips and jaw don't affect this sound,
嘴唇和下巴不影响这个音，
so your mouth can be in position for the next sound when you're making the H.
所以当你发 H 音时，你的嘴可以为下一个音做好准备。
For example, the word how.
例如，单词 how。
How.
How。
The lips, jaw, and tongue take the beginning position of the OW as in NOW diphthong.
嘴唇、下巴和舌头取 OW 如 NOW 双元音的起始位置。
H, how.
H，how。
Let's look up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察。
The sound by itself.
单独的声音。
The jaw is relaxed and the lips part.
下巴放松，嘴唇分开。
The word high.
单词 high。
There's nothing to see at the beginning of this word.
在这个词的开头没有什么可看的。
The H sound happens without changing what the lips do for the AI as in BY diphthong.
H 音发生时不改变嘴唇为 AI 如 BY 双元音所做的动作。
The word who.
单词 who。
Again, there's nothing to see at the beginning of this word.
同样，在这个词的开头没有什么可看的。
The H sound happens without changing what the lips do for the next sound.
H 音发生时不改变嘴唇为下一个音所做的动作。
The OO as in BOO vowel.
OO 如 BOO 元音。
The H sound.
H 音。
High.
High。
Who.
Who。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Hope.
Hope。
History.
History。
Ahead.
Ahead。
Behind.
Behind。
Here.
Here。
Somehow.
Somehow。